Guide to the Faculty Minutes RG.018
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
Faculty Minutes
1896 - present
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn
Polytechnic Institute of New York
Polytechnic Institute of New York University
Polytechnic University (Brooklyn, New York, N.Y.)
RG.018
18
9 Cubic Feet
The Faculty Minutes contain meeting minutes and related documents to Polytechnic faculty meetings. The minutes reflect the name changes of the institution from the Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn (PIB) to the Polytechnic Institute of New York (PINY) to Polytechnic University, and, finally, to the Polytechnic Institute of New York University.
Arrangement
Faculty Minutes are arranged by date into three series. Series I (1896-1975) contains the earliest faculty minutes and notes, which are bound. Series II (1962-1985) contains faculty minutes and notes in binders. Series III (1986-present) contains foldered faculty minutes and notes in boxes.
Biographical / Historical
The Faculty Minutes collection begins in 1896 in bound volumes. Over the years, the minutes were no longer bound, but were placed in three ring binders. The most recent faculty minutes and associated documents are foldered and boxed immediately after the meeting. Faculty meeting minutes from 2003 to present are also available online, although they are password protected so that only faculty members may view them.
The minutes reflect changes in the institution over time, including faculty appointments, graduation lists, proposed and accepted courses, and other issues related to the operation of the university.
Scope and Contents
The Faculty Minutes contain both meeting minutes and other associated documents from faculty meetings. The minutes span from 1896 to the present and are available as bound items, binders, and loose paper documents.
Conditions Governing Access
Access is restricted to faculty.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Materials found in collection; there is no documentation concerning the provenance of these materials.
- Series I: Bound volumes, 1896-1975; 6643
  - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn Faculty Minutes, 1896-1913, 1896 September - 1913 March; 6644 (Volume PIB bound 1)
  - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn Faculty Minutes, 1913-1927, 1913 April - 1927 October; 6645 (Volume PIB bound 2)
  - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn Faculty Minutes, 1927-1936, 1927 November - 1936 April; 6646 (Volume PIB bound 3)
  - Graduate Committee Minutes, 1928-1938, 1928 February - 1938 December; 6647 (Volume PIB bound 3)
  - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn Faculty Minutes, 1936-1943, 1936 april - 1943 December; 6648 (Volume PIB bound 4)
  - Graduate Faculty Minutes, 1939-1943, 1939 February - 1943 December; 6649 (Volume PIB bound 5)
  - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn Faculty Minutes and Graduate Faculty Minutes, 1944-1956, 1944 February - 1956 November; 6650 (Volume PIB bound 6)
  - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn Faculty Minutes and Graduate Faculty Minutes, 1957-1961, 1957 June - 1961 April; 6651 (Volume PIB bound 7)
  - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn Faculty Minutes, 1961-1963, 1961 June - 1963 December; 6652 (Volume PIB bound 8)
  - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn Faculty Minutes, 1964-1966, 1964 January - 1966 June; 6653 (Volume PIB bound 9)
  - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn Faculty Minutes, 1966-1968, 1966 September - 1968 June; 6654 (Volume PIB bound 10)
  - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn Faculty Minutes, 1968-1969, 1968 September - 1969 March; 6655 (Volume PIB bound 11 (temporary))
  - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn Faculty Minutes, 1969-1970, 1969 September - 1970 July; 6656 (Volume PIB bound 11)
  - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn Faculty Minutes, 1969-1970, 1969 May - 1970 June; 6657 (Volume PIB bound 12 (temporary))
  - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn Faculty Minutes, 1970-1971, 1970 September - 1971 August; 6658 (Volume PIB bound 12)
  - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn Faculty Minutes, 1971-1972, 1971 September - 1972 July; 6659 (Volume PIB bound 13)
  - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn Faculty Minutes, 1972-1973, 1972 September - 1973 June; 6660 (Volume PIB bound 14)
  - Polytechnic Institute of New York Faculty Minutes, 1973-1974, 1973 August - 1974 May; 6661 (Volume PINY bound 1)
  - Polytechnic Institute of New York Faculty Minutes, 1974-1975, 1974 September - 1975 June; 6662 (Volume PINY bound 2)
- Series II: Binders, 1962-1985; 6663
  - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn Faculty Minutes, 1962-1963, 1962 November - 1963 December; 6664 (Volume Binder 1)
  - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn Faculty Minutes, 1964, 1964 March - December; 6665 (Volume Binder 2)
  - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn Faculty Minutes, Spring 1965, 1965 February - June; 6666 (Volume Binder 3)
  - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn Faculty Minutes, Fall 1965, 1965 June - September; 6667 (Volume Binder 4)
  - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn Faculty Minutes, 1966-1967, 1966 September - 1967 May; 6669 (Volume Binder 5)
  - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn Faculty Minutes, 1967-1968, 1967 September - 1968 May; 6670 (Volume Binder 6)
  - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn Faculty Minutes, 1968-1969, 1968 September - 1969 May; 6671 (Volume Binder 7)
  - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn Faculty Minutes, 1969-1970, 1969 September - 1970 June; 6672 (Volume Binder 8)
  - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn Faculty Minutes, 1970-1971, 1970 October - 1971 June; 6673 (Volume Binder 9)
  - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn Faculty Minutes, 1971-1972, 1971 September - 1972 July; 6674 (Volume Binder 10)
  - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn Faculty Minutes, 1972-1973, 1972 September - 1973 June; 6675 (Volume Binder 11)
  - [Polytechnic Institute of New York] Faculty Minutes, 1973-1974, 1976, 1973 August - 1974 May, 1976 April; 6676 (Volume Binder 12)
  - [Polytechnic Institute of New York] Faculty Minutes, 1974-1976, 1974 September - 1976 June; 6677 (Volume Binder 13)
  - [Polytechnic Institute of New York] Faculty Minutes Duplicates, 1974-1975, 1974 September - 1975 May; 6678 (Volume Binder 14)
  - [Polytechnic Institute of New York] Faculty Minutes, 1975-1976, 1975 September - 1976 May; 6679 (Volume Binder 15)
  - [Polytechnic Institute of New York] Faculty Minutes, 1976-1978, 1976 September - 1978 March; 6680 (Volume Binder 16)
  - [Polytechnic Institute of New York] Faculty Minutes, 1976-1978, 1976 September - 1978 May; 6681 (Volume Binder 17)
  - [Polytechnic Institute of New York] Faculty Minutes, 1978-1979, 1978 September - 1979 June; 6682 (Volume Binder 18)
  - [Polytechnic Institute of New York] Faculty Minutes, 1979-1980, 1979 September - 1980 June; 6683 (Volume Binder 19)
  - [Polytechnic Institute of New York] Faculty Minutes, 1980-1981, 1980 July - 1981 May; 6684 (Volume Binder 20)
  - [Polytechnic Institute of New York] Faculty Minutes, 1981-1982, 1981 September - 1982 April; 6685 (Volume Binder 21)
  - [Polytechnic Institute of New York] Faculty Minutes, 1981-1983, 1981 August - 1983 May; 6686 (Volume Binder 22)
  - [Polytechnic Institute of New York] Faculty Meeting, 9/14/83, 1983 September 14; 6687 (Volume Binder 23)
  - [Polytechnic Institute of New York] Faculty Meeting, 1/25/84, 1984 January 25; 6688 (Volume Binder 24)
  - [Polytechnic Institute of New York] Faculty Meeting Working, 1/25/84, 1984 January 25; 6689 (Volume Binder 25)
  - [Polytechnic Institute of New York] Faculty Minutes, September 14, 1983, 1983 September 14; 6690 (Volume Binder 26)
  - [Polytechnic Institute of New York] Faculty Minutes, 1984, 1984, January-October; 6691 (Volume Binder 27)
  - [Polytechnic Institute of New York] Faculty Minutes, 1985, 1985 February-November; 6692 (Volume Binder 28)
  - [Polytechnic Institute of New York] Faculty Minutes Duplicates, 1980-1981, 1980 September - 1981 July; 6693 (Volume Binder 29)
- Series III: Boxes, 1986 - present; 6668
  - Faculty Minutes, January 22, 1986, 6694 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Minutes, March 12, 1986, 6695 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Minutes, September 10, 1986, 6696 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Minutes, December 3, 1986, 6697 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Minutes, January 19, 1987, 6698 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Minutes, January 21, 1987, 6699 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Minutes, January 28, 1987, 6700 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Minutes, February 2, 1987, 6701 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Minutes, February 18, 1987, 6702 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Minutes, March 11, 1987, 6704 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Minutes, March 25, 1987, 6706 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Minutes, April 1, 1987, 6707 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Minutes, April 13, 1987, 6710 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Minutes, April 23, 1987, 6711 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Minutes, April 29, 1987, 6712 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Faculty Minutes, April 30, 1987, 6713 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 11, 1987, 6714 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 11, 1987, 6715 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Faculty Minutes, September 9, 1987, 6717 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Faculty Minutes, October 31, 1987, 6718 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Faculty Minutes, December 2, 1987, 6719 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Faculty Minutes, January 27, 1988, 6720 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Minutes, March 2,1988, 6721 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Minutes, March 23, 1988, 6722 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 25, 1988, 6723 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Minutes, November 30, 1988, 6724 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Minutes, January 25, 1989, 6725 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Minutes, March 16, 1989, 6726 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Minutes, March 22,1989, 6727 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 16, 1989, 6728 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 24, 1989, 6729 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Minutes, July 31, 1989, 6730 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Minutes, September 13, 1989, 6731 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Minutes, October 6, 1989, 6732 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Minutes, October 12, 1989, 6733 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Minutes, April 4, 1990, 1989; 6734 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Minutes, April 25, 1990, 6735 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 10, 1990, 6736 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 16, 1990, 6737 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 21, 1990, 6738 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 23, 1990, 6739 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Faculty Minutes, October 10, 1990, 6741 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Faculty Minutes, November 28, 1990, 6742 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Faculty Minutes, July 17, 1987, 6716 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Faculty Minutes, Decemeber 3, 1990, 6743 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Faculty Minutes, January 23, 1991, 6744 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Faculty Minutes, February 8,1991, 6745 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Faculty Minutes, February 20,1991, 6746 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Faculty Minutes, March 26, 1991, 6747 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 2, 1991, 6748 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 10, 1991, 6749 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 13, 1991, 6750 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 22, 1991, 6751 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 29, 1991, 6752 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Faculty Minutes, June 28, 1991, 6753 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Faculty Minutes, February 10, 1992, 6754 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Faculty Minutes, October 5, 1994, 6755 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Faculty Minutes, October 2, 1996, 6756 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Minutes, October 16, 1996, 6757 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Minutes, December 4, 1996, 6758 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Minutes, December 11, 1996, 6759 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Minutes, February 12, 1997, 6760 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Minutes, March 26, 1997, 6761 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Minutes, April 23, 1997, 6762 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 7, 1997, 6763 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Minutes, September 10,1997, 6764 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Minutes, October 15, 1997, 6765 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Minutes, November 5, 1997, 6766 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Minutes, December 3, 1997, 6767 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Minutes, February 4, 1998, 6768 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Minutes, February 11, 1998, 6769 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Minutes, March 5, 1998, 6770 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Minutes, April 1, 1998, 6771 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 6, 1998, 6772 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Faculty Minutes, September 1, 1998, 6773 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Faculty Minutes, September 9, 1998, 6774 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Faculty Minutes, September 9, 1998 (duplicates), 6775 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Faculty Minutes, October 14, 1998, 6776 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Faculty Minutes, February 3, 1999, 6777 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Minutes, March 17, 1999, 6778 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Minutes, April 21, 1999, 6779 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 19, 1999, 6780 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 26, 1999, 6781 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Minutes, September 22, 1999, 6782 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Minutes, October 20, 1999, 6783 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Minutes, November 15, 1999, 6784 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Minutes, November 17, 1999, 6785 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Minutes, December 15, 1999, 6786 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Minutes, February 2, 2000, 6787 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Minutes, March, 1, 2000, 6788 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Minutes, March 1, 2000 (duplicates), 6789 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Minutes, April 5, 2000, 6790 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 3, 2000, 6791 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 17, 2000, 6792 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 17, 2000 (duplicates), 6793 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Faculty Minutes, November 1, 2000, 6794 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Faculty Minutes, November 1, 2000 (duplicates), 6795 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Faculty Minutes, December 6, 2000, 6796 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Minutes, December 6, 2000 (duplicates), 6797 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Minutes, December 6, 2000 (duplicates), 6798 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Minutes, February 7, 2001, 6799 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Minutes, March 2, 2001, 6800 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Minutes, March 7, 2001, 6801 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Minutes, March 7, 2001 (duplicates), 6803 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Minutes, March 15, 2001, 6802 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Minutes, April 4, 2001, 6804 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Minutes, April 4, 2001 (duplicates), 6805 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Minutes, April 25, 2001, 6806 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Minutes, April 25, 2001 (duplicates), 6807 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 2, 2001, 6808 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Minutes, November 7, 2001, 6809 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Minutes, November 7, 2001 (duplicates), 6810 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Minutes, December 12, 2001, 6811 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Minutes, December 12, 2001 (duplicates), 6812 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Minutes, March 5, 2002, 6813 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Minutes, March 6, 2002, 6814 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Minutes, March 7, 2002, 6815 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Minutes, April 2, 2002, 6816 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Minutes, April 3, 2002, 6817 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Minutes, April 3, 2002 (duplicates), 6818 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 1, 2002, 6819 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Minutes, June 3, 2002, 6820 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Minutes, September 18, 2002, 6821 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Minutes, October 9, 2002, 6822 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Minutes, October 9, 2002 (duplicates), 6823 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Minutes, November 22, 2002, 6824 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Minutes, December 4, 2002, 6825 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Minutes, December 4, 2002 (duplicates), 6826 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Minutes, January 5, 2003, 6827 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Minutes, February 5, 2003, 6828 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Minutes, February 5, 2003 (duplicates), 6829 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Minutes, February 14, 2003, 6830 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Minutes, March 5, 2003, 6831 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 7, 2003, 6832 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 13, 2003, 6833 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Minutes, September 10, 2003, 6834 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Minutes, September 10, 2003 (duplicates), 6835 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Minutes, October 1, 2003, 6836 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Minutes, November 15, 2003, 6837 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Minutes, December 1, 2003, 6838 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Minutes, January 29, 2004, 6840 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Minutes, January 29, 2004 (duplicates), 6841 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Minutes, February 5, 2004, 6842 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Minutes, February 5, 2004 (duplicates), 6843 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Minutes, March 3, 2004, 6844 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Minutes, March 3, 2004 (duplicates), 6845 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Minutes, April 1, 2004, 6846 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Minutes, April 14, 2004, 6847 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Minutes, April 14, 2004 (duplicates), 6848 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 5, 2004, 6849 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 5, 2004 (duplicates), 6850 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Minutes, September 22, 2004, 6851 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Minutes, September 22, 2004 (duplicates), 6852 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Minutes, November 3, 2004, 6853 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Minutes, November 3, 2004 (duplicates), 6854 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Minutes, December 1, 2004, 6855 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Minutes, December 1, 2004 (duplicates), 6856 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Minutes, December 8, 2004, 6857 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Minutes, December 8, 2004 (duplicates), 6858 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Minutes, December 15, 2004, 6859 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Minutes, December 15, 2004 (duplicates), 6860 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Minutes, January 19, 2005, 6861 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Minutes, January 19, 2005 (duplicates), 6862 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Minutes, January 26, 2005, 6863 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Minutes, January 26, 2005 (duplicates), 6864 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Minutes, Febraury 7, 2005, 6865 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Minutes, March 15, 2005, 6866 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 2, 2005, 6867 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 2, 2005 (duplicates), 6868 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 4, 2005, 6869 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 4, 2005 (duplicates), 6870 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 6, 2005, 6871 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 6, 2005 (duplicates), 6872 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Minutes, September 7, 2005, 6873 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Minutes, October 12, 2005, 6874 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Minutes, November 2, 2005, 6875 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Minutes, December 7, 2005, 6876 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Minutes, February 1, 2006, 6877 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Minutes, April 5, 2006, 6878 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Minutes, September 13, 2006, 6879 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Minutes, October 16, 2006, 6880 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Minutes, November 1, 2006, 6881 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Minutes, December 6, 2006, 6882 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Minutes, December 6, 2006 (duplicates), 6883 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Minutes, January 31, 2007, 6884 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Minutes, February 26, 2007, 6885 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Minutes, February 26, 2007 (duplicates), 6886 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Minutes, March 7, 2007, 6887 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Minutes, March 7, 2007 (duplicates), 6888 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Minutes, March 23, 2007, 6889 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Minutes, March 23, 2007 (duplicates), 6890 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Minutes, April 11, 2007, 6891 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Minutes, April 11, 2007 (duplicates), 6892 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 2, 2007, 6893 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 2, 2007 (duplicates), 6894 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Minutes, August 15, 2007, 6895 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Minutes, August 15, 2007 (duplicates), 6896 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Minutes, September 5, 2007, 6897 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Minutes, September 5, 2007 (duplicates), 6898 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Minutes, September 19, 2007, 6899 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Minutes, September 26, 2007, 6900 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Minutes, September 26, 2007 (duplicates), 6901 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Minutes, October 3, 2007, 6902 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Minutes, October 3, 2007 (duplicates), 6903 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Minutes, December 5, 2007, 6904 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Minutes, December 5, 2007 (duplicates), 6905 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Minutes, February 6, 2008, 6906 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Minutes, March 5, 2008, 6907 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Minutes, April 2, 2008, 6908 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 14, 2008, 6909 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 14, 2008 (duplicates), 6910 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Minutes, September 10. 2008, 6911 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Minutes, September 10, 2008 (duplicates), 6912 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Minutes, October 1, 2008, 6913 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Minutes, October 1, 2008 (duplicates), 6914 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Minutes, November 5, 2008, 6915 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Minutes, December 3, 2008, 6916 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Minutes, February 4, 2009, 6917 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Minutes, February 4, 2009 (duplicates), 6918 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Minutes, March 4, 2009, 6919 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Minutes, March 4, 2009 (duplicates), 6920 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Minutes, March 4, 2009 (duplicates), 6921 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Minutes, April 1, 2009, 6922 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Minutes, April 1, 2009 (duplicates), 6923 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Minutes, April 8, 2009, 6924 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Minutes, April 8, 2009 (duplicates), 6925 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Minutes, April 29, 2009, 6926 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Minutes, November 9, 2009, 6927 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Minutes, November 9, 2009 (duplicates), 6928 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Minutes, December 2, 2009, 6929 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Minutes, December 2, 2009 (duplicates), 6930 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Minutes, April 7, 2010, 6931 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 5, 2010, 6932 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 5, 2010 (duplicates), 6933 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Minutes, October 6, 2010, 6934 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Minutes, October 6, 2010 (duplicates), 6935 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Minutes, November 3, 2010, 6936 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Minutes, November 3, 2010 (duplicates), 6937 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Minutes, December 1, 2010, 6938 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Minutes, December 1, 2010 (duplicates), 6939 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Minutes, December 10, 2010, 6940 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Minutes, February 2, 2011, 6941 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Minutes, February 2, 2011 (duplicates), 6942 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Minutes, March 2, 2011, 6943 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Minutes, March 2, 2011 (duplicates), 6944 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Minutes, April 6, 2011, 6945 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Minutes, April 6, 2011 (duplicates), 6946 (Box 19, Folder 16)